You can't escape history.
Donner Pass is a horror film directed by Elise Robertson.
Donner Pass has a well-known and macabre history - the place where George Donner and his party got stuck
in the winter of 1846 and were forced to resort to cannibalism to keep from starving.
But what if it wasn't just history?
Kayley, played by Desiree Hall.
Thomas, played by Erik Stocklin.
Nicole, played by Adelaide Kane.
Valerie, played by Krystal Davis.
Donner Pass is a 7,056-foot-high (2,151 m) mountain pass in the northern Sierra Nevada, above Donner
Lake and Donner Memorial State Park about 9 miles (14 km) west of Truckee, California.
Like the Sierra Nevada itself, the pass has a steep approach from
the east and a gradual approach from the west.
The pass has been used by the California Trail, First transcontinental railroad,
Overland Route, Lincoln Highway and Victory Highway (both later U.S.
Route 40 and still later Donner Pass Road), as
well as indirectly by Interstate 80.
The pass gets its name from the ill-fated Donner
Party who overwintered there in 1846.
Today, the area is home to a thriving recreational community with several alpine
lakes and ski resorts (Donner Ski Ranch, Boreal, and Sugar Bowl).
The permanent communities in the area include Kingvale and Soda Springs, as well
as the larger community below the pass surrounding Donner Lake.
The film explores themes of curse, cannibal, vanity project, woman director.
The tone is dark.